Through the example of two youths, Dororo and Hyakkimaru,
this story will depict the lives of people in the chaos of war.
Dororo is an orphaned child.
Hyakkimaru has had 48 parts of his body, including his limbs,
stolen from him by demons.
But, after being raised by a doctor named Jukou,
he leaves on a journey to slay the demons and reclaim his body.
Note that this film is a digest version, not the main feature.
Dororo
The name of this young man is Hyakkimaru.
To properly acquaint you with Hyakkimaru,
we must turn back to his origins.
O 48 devils, O demons, hear my plea.
I seek to rule! By any means necessary!
Lend unto me your power, that I may make this country my own!
In return, I will reward you with whatever you desire.
Yes. I will give you my child.
My child's eyes, nose, mouth, hands, feet...
You may divide them amongst yourselves as you please!
O 48 demons,
you may take from my child's body whichever 48 pieces please you.
What? Was it born?
My end of the bargain is fulfilled.
They've carved up my son as promised!
Now this country will be mine!
Throw that monstrosity away! It's an impediment to my rise!
You call him a monster?
Th-This boy is your son!
He is not! Now dispose of that monster!
Hyakkimaru... Hyakkimaru...
Who's there?
You have 48 demons stalking you.
Answer me!
There are 48 pieces of your body missing.
Who goes there?
How do you know all that?
Show yourself!
Defeat the 48 demons.
If you can, your body will return to that of a normal human.
What?
He said if I can slay 48 demons I can be a normal human.
One...
Save me!
Someone come save me!
That's two.
Bro!
That was some impressive swordsmanship there!
Those swords you've got on your arms are especially stunning.
With how sharp they are, I'll bet they fetch a pretty price, huh?
What? Did I say something that offended you?
Kid, hurry up and beat it already.
Ha ha ha and hah!
I've decided I'm gonna swipe your swords.
What? You? Take these swords?
You've got that right.
I may not look it, but I'm the famous kid thief, Dororo.
Once I set my eyes on something, come war or dump truck collision,
I've got to make it mine or no one'll respect me.
Kid, no good is going to come from following me around.
Yeah, right! I'm not going to back down that easily.
The grim reaper stalks me.
Is that right? Well, now I want to follow you more than ever!
Sounds like fun!
Go away.
Not gonna happen!
Whatever happens isn't my problem.
Like I'd ever count on you for help!
Thus begins Hyakkimaru and Dororo's strange journey.
No! No outsiders may enter this village!
I have strict orders from Lady Bandai to that effect.
- Go on! Turn back around! - Get lost!
What's your problem? I'm just going through!
This brat isn't listening! Tie them up!
Just what did we do wrong?!
Let's hear it, huh?
Where are the two of you bound for?
I'm going demon slaying with Bro here!
There are no monsters in this village.
This is exactly the kind of town I'd expect to find a monster in.
Leave this village peacefully.
I don't think so.
I suppose this cannot be helped then.
Then tie them up in the well house as per usual.
Tch, what's their problem?
It makes no darn sense.
For starters, that Bandai woman is--
I'm hearing something from the bottom of the well.
Bro, it's coming!
Oh no! Did I let it get away?
I could feel that I landed a hit though.
Bro, let's try going inside the well.
It's possible this well is connected to the inside of the mansion.
Ah! Bro! It came out inside the mansion like you thought!
Ah, we found it!
So you've seen me!
B-Bro, it's here!
Demon, you've shown your true colors at last!
Are you not terrified of me?
Not in the least.
I, Hyakkimaru, eagerly look forward to meeting demons like yourself.
Because I want to become fully human as soon as I can!
B-Bro, the roof is caving in!
Curse you, demon! The mansion was a fake too?
Now that you know what I am, I cannot let you live!
Just try to get closer. I'll crush you under this bell!
Dororo, now!
That's three.
Bro, is something wrong?
My arm...
Huh? Y-your arm? What's wrong with your arm, Bro?
Ah! The sword...!
Bro! Your arm!
I grew an arm!
This is... my arm!
Dororo, it's my arm!
Look, Dororo!
It's my arm!
Final Episode
"The Last Demon"
Storyboard (Digest Version)
Special Feature Music
"The Song of Hyakkimaru”
Sung by: Kimihiko Aoi
"The Song of Dororo”
Alternate Version
Dororo and
Hyakkimaru
Episode 26
The Final Demon
The scarlet clouds shine in my eyes
I want to live as a normal person too
This is the song of the merciless wind
When it howls, it howls with the voice of a demon
The shooting stars shine in my eyes
I want to call someone mother too
This is the song of the wind of harsh destiny
It blows onwards, vanishing across the burned plains