Toei Co. Ltd. Presents
Stop it! Please. Forgive me.
Don't kill me. Please.
For God's sake, please.
Here. Captain Sminny!
Over here.
This is the victim.
Same way as the last case.
Chief, it looks like it's the same killer.
Let's get going.
Only one minute to go.
No ship in sight.
He won't show up.
Golgo 13!
I was expecting you. I'm Rocky Brown.
Sorry. I should know not to shake hands.
You don't give your hand to others.
That's Golgo 13.
It's a sinister name.
It means the 13th man who gave
the crown of thorns to Christ,
and drove him to death on Golgotha Hill.
That's the origin of his name.
He won't attract attention in Hong Kong.
Is he Japanese?
I don't know.
His nationality, real name, age
and birthplace are unknown.
All we know is that he speaks seven languages.
He's a perfect professional sniper
who never misses his target.
Golgo 13, what are you doing?
They're my men.
He's aiming at us.
It's 500 metres away.
The bullet will never reach.
I sald this was a secret meeting.
- I'm sorry. Listen to me.
I'll pay another $50,000.
No one else can do this job.
Put out to sea.
I want you to rub out Chou,
our Hong Kong head man.
He's supposed to process drugs
gathered in Southeast Asia
and send them to our US Headquarters.
But we've heard that he's selling
them through his own channels.
We ordered him to Headquarters, but he refused.
On top of that, he killed the killers
we sent after him.
Three able killers, you know.
We have to finish this job quickly,
as the Hong Kong Police are investigating.
Sminny, the drugs detective.
He's passionate about controlling drugs.
He's a tough one.
In between Sminny and us...
Chou may betray us for his own safety.
Get him before the police do.
Why?
I've memorised his face.
So you accept the job?
$150,000 will be transferred
to your bank account in Switzerland.
- Golgo 13: Kuron no Kubi ~
GOLGO 13: KOWLOON ASSIGNMENT
Original comic: SAITO Takao
Screenplay:
NAKAJIMA Nobunaki & MATSUMOTO Isao
Cinematography: AKAMATSU Shigeru
Art Direction: IGAWA Tokumichi
Music: IBE Harumi
In co-operation with
Chia-Lun Motion Picture Co.
Cast
CHIBA Shinichi
Chia-Lun
SHIHOMI Etsuko
SHINDO Emi
Eleanor Sun, Dana
Wei-Chi, Jerry ITOH
TSURUTA Koji
Director: NODA Yukio
I'll borrow this.
What are you doing? Hey!
Who is your boss?
Move.
That way.
Stop it!
- Be quiet and line up.
Put your hands on the table.
Be quiet.
Hey. Turn around.
As I've explained, we've uncovered
a number of dope peddling routes.
Your conclusion?
They all boil down to the same man.
Who is it?
- He's a Hong Kong celebrity.
Chou... Lei... Feng.
Chou?
We'd better check it again.
Sminny, are you saying that Mr Chou
was involved in those killings?
Yes, I am.
The dead were from a US drugs
syndicate. Chou must be in trouble.
This is a chance to clear Hong Kong of drugs.
Any evidence?
They are clever, leaving no clear trace.
But Mr Chou is...
Chief. Stop calling him "Mr" Chou.
He's a big shot, involved
in many tourist businesses.
Be careful investigating him.
That's all.
We'd better search again.
Good evening.
- It's been a long time.
Welcome. Please make yourself at home.
How have you been?
Excuse me for a minute.
Have a good time.
Wonderful.
Mr Chou.
Headquarters seem to have sent another killer.
Who Is it?
- Our source doesn't know him.
Take it easy. We have a
complete list of HQ's killers.
We'll know once they are in Hong Kong.
Will they repeat the same errors
for the fourth time?
What do you mean?
They might have hired a new killer.
They need to do something different.
Don't worry. Hong Kong is my garden.
Any man they send will be
floating in the sea the next day.
Isn't that right, Chali, Nyudo?
I'm counting on you guys.
Ching, are the goods ready?
They'll be shipped tomorrow
Will you check them?
All right, I'm coming now.
Sminny.
This is Lin-Li. I'm trailing Chou's car.
I just passed Water Road. I
think I'm onto something.
Be careful.
Contact me if anything happens.
Hello, Boss.
Is the purity okay?
- Yes, Boss.
Are you sure?
- Yes, sir.
Stand up!
Chief.
Any news?
- No.
Anything from her?
-No...
Call her again.
Calm down, Sminny.
How can I?
It's been two hours since
we lost communication.
Chief, let me arrest Chou.
What are you saying?
We can make up some excuse.
Kidnapping Lin-Li, or something.
If anything happens to her...
Calm down. She might be safe.
If we rush now, everything
we've done will be in vain.
Where are you going?
Sorry, we're closed.
Police. Move!
I'll be in trouble if I let you in, sir.
Even the police?
- Evening.
Welcome, Detective. Please come in.
Excuse his rudeness.
Bring sake.
I want to see your husband.
Urgent business?
- He knows.
I wonder if he is I, as he's quite busy...
Detective Sminny.
- Come to the station.
Me?
- Just come.
What did I do?
- Get ready.
Do you have a warrant?
I'm willing to co-operate with you
as a good citizen.
But it's an unjustifiable request, isn't it?
How about a drink?
We'll unmask you soon.
CHOU DONATES PUBLIC POOL
HONG KONG TO HOLD CEREMONY
Mr Duke Togo. We've taken
your parcels to your room.
Thank you.
SAMPLE: ELECTRIC DRILL
SAMPLE: GAS BURNER
We have special guests tonight -
Mr Polansky, Poranian Consul,
and his daughter, Maria.
Here they are. Mr Polansky and Maria.
Thank you.
Let us play some Poranian folk songs for you.
Band, get ready.
Nice, isn't it?
- Yes.
I'm full. May I go and see the pictures?
Go ahead.
What's the matter?
You have the same eyes as the dragon.
They look strong.
Maria, Papa is going.
- Already? No fun.
Let's go.
Excuse us.
You've been very good today, Maria.
Time to go home with your father.
Let's go.
You scoundrel! What have you done?
1told you not to touch my sister!
Shut up!
She killed herself because of you.
That's none of my business.
You brute!
I'll kill you.
Gunshots!
This way!
He's dead.
- He took three shots.
Did you see anything?
- Yeah.
I saw the moment he was shot.
He went that way.
What did he look like?
- A young man, flamboyantly dressed.
Excuse me.
- Captain!
Any witnesses?
- That couple.
Are you a tourist?
-Yes.
Your name and hotel, please.
Duke Togo. Room 1002, Melrie Hotel.
Who is she?
1 picked her up on the street.
Why did you save me?
Did you want me to tell the truth?
- I don't mean that.
Thank you very much.
Hand her over to us.
She killed our friend. She was his woman.
Get him.
How much does Sminny know?
What a nerve you've got!
I admire you, Detective.
But we won't kill you until you speak up.
What's the matter?
What happened?
A terrible guy has shown up.
Nyudo was shot in the forehead.
Was he killed?
He's awfully strong.
- What does he look like?
He's either Japanese or
Chinese, with sharp eyes.
He must be the new killer.
What? Go and get him.
Search every part of town.
HONG KONG PUBLIC POOL:
OPENS 10 AUGUST
Lin-Lit
This is Sminny.
Is that you, Lin-Li?
No, I'm not Lin-Li.
- Who is this?
We...
We came here to play and found this thing.
Where are you? Tell me.
We're at the scrapyard near the duck pond.
Stop shooting, Sminny!
Or the girl's dead.
Throw your gun away.
Shit!
Firel
I can't see.
Watch out!
Lin-Lit
What a mess, Chou.
But we left no trace. The plant blew up.
But you should be aware that
the police are getting close.
And you haven't dealt with the killer from HQ.
I have an idea about who the killer is.
Who is it?
He's an Oriental man with sharp eyes,
an amazing karate master.
He shot Nyudo right in the forehead.
Right in the forehead?
What's the matter?
He must be Golgo 13.
Golgo 137
You must have heard of him.
He's the top professional sniper.
If you know that much, you can easily find him.
No. He won't reveal himself.
He has never missed a target.
Do something, please.
An Oriental with sharp eyes...
All right. You go abroad and hide, Chou.
Wait till the storm is over, then come back here.
You have enough money to idle
for a couple of years, don't you?
I think so.
I'll make arrangements for you to fly out
after the pool opening ceremony tomorrow.
Do I still need to attend the ceremony?
Don't lose your courage.
Tomorrow is your day.
It can't be done without you.
It's for Lin-Li, who was killed.
Cough up your money. Don't be stingy.
Here's 10 bucks.
Hello? Hold the line.
Captain, it's for you.
Mr Sminny. Do you know Golgo 13?
Golgo 137
He isn't a stranger to you, is he?
Who the hell are you? What's your name?
Golgo 13 is in Hong Kong now.
Did you know that?
What?
That's all. Good night.
How was it?
Well done.
Who's Golgo 13?
A professional killer. He's in town.
Have you met him?
No. But he owes me something.
Three years ago
I was ordered to guard a diplomat.
We were informed that
Golgo 13 was targeting him.
The diplomat didn't want me around
but I never left his side.
But when he was about to leave...
Mr Wang.
Good morning.
Golgo 13 is here to kill Chou.
We have to arrest Chou before he's killed.
Chou killed Lin-Li, no doubt about it.
Get a warrant immediately.
OK. We'll bring him In. But
after the pool opening.
That'll be too late.
The ceremony is being held by the city.
The authorities won't arrest Chou, the donator.
Don't you see?
PUBLIC POOL
OPENING CEREMONY
To promote sports
and for citizens' health,
this pool is a magnificent present given to us.
Let me introduce Mr Chou,
who gave us this wonderful pool.
Hi.
To show our gratitude, we'd like
to present a bouquet to Mr Chou.
From Maria, the daughter of
Mr Polansky, the Poranian Consul.
Here you are.
Thank you.
To commemorate the opening,
we're holding a 100-meter race
with Olympic swimmers.
Mr Chou will fire the starter pistol.
Cuff him after this.
- Okay.
Ready!
Golgo 13 did it.
Hurry!
DENTAL CLINIC
CLOSED
Rocky Brown?
Who did you get to kill Chou?
What?
I didn't hire anyone but you.
No one has ever cheated me like that.
I would never cheat you.
I know full well what would happen
if I double-crossed you.
Believe me Golgo 13.
Who did it, anyway?
My target is the biggest boss
in Hong Kong, right?
Is there a boss above Chou?
- That would explain it.
Find the man and get him.
I'll pay another $100,000 into your bank account.
Please.
Who could it be?
Have you finished, Golgo?
This is too much.
Take it. It was a long distance call.
Thanks for coming.
You remind me of my younger days.
It's been 30 years since the war.
I've been wandering places with a gun.
I lost the chance to return to Japan,
and settled here in the end.
Stay here as long as you like.
It's an old man's whining.
Good evening.
I was here last night, too.
You were? Thank you. Enjoy the evening.
Good evening.
You were the one who
became friends with Maria.
You look happy, despite
your husband being dead.
Do you want to know why?
I can tell you only when we are alone.
Chou was worthless as a man.
He didn't deserve to be loved,
if he counldn't give me joy.
Who deserves it, then?
You, hon. It's you now.
I like a strong man like you.
Next time, make sure the killer
wears the same perfume as you.
Make the phone call.
There must be a man waiting for your report.
Tell him it's over.
This is Li-Hua.
Is it over?
Yes.
Was that the man you told me about?
Hello?
Li-Hua. What's the matter?
Hello? Hello? What's up, Li-Hua?
Anything new?
- Nothing.
A man who looks like Golgo
appeared at the airport.
What?
- He's on a plane to Tokyo.
Didn't they stop him?
No, his papers were impeccable,
so there was no excuse to.
Control tower.
- Stop the Tokyo plane.
It's too late.
It just took off on schedule.
One, two, three, four...
... five, six, seven, eight,
nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen...
Oh, Uncle Dragon Eyes!
We are on the same plane.
That's beautiful
Thank you, Uncle.
Uncle gave me this brooch.
How nice.
Hello, American Embassy?
Mr Arnold, the First Secretary, please.
This is Polansky. Just Polansky. He'll know.
I have urgent business.
With the ambassador? Where are you going?
TOKYO AIRPORT
I'm Tachibana, of Police International Liaison.
I'm Sminny.
- I'm Miki.
Brother!
Hit
This is my sister. She's studying in Tokyo.
How are you?
Unfortunately, we missed Togo by a second.
I'm sorry for not being able to help.
Are you sure? Okay.
He stayed at the Asia Hotel last night.
But he checked out this morning.
We noticed something.
Here's the ledger of the Asia Hotel.
We checked it against the passenger
list of his flight.
There was another person listed on both.
Who was it?
Polansky, the Poranian Consul
in Hong Kong and his daughter.
Polansky? Where is he now?
He also went to Kyoto,
leaving the daughter at the hotel.
Who is this man named Duke Togo?
His last name sounds Japanese, but...
Brother, you're as daring as ever.
-Am 1?
Going to Kyoto straight after arriving in Tokyo.
Well, that gave me a reason to travel.
That's why you volunteered
to be my guide, huh?
You had a strong sense of
justice even as a child,
but you were very rough.
Now yon're a cop going after a crook.
Could have been the other way round.
Silly. How long Is it to Kyoto?
- Two more hours.
A slow train.
- Oh?
This bullet train is running at 200km/h.
KYOTO POLICE
Good day, sir.
I have to go now. Enjoy sightseeing.
You found the criminal?
- Show me the town next time.
Take care.
- You, too.
Say hello to the Hong Kong people.
Goodbye.
I want asylum in the US, as I'm in danger.
You can count on my great souvenirs.
The FBI will be excited.
What are the souvenirs?
The list of who's In the drug
syndicates in the US and Hong Kong.
The reply?
The matter is serious.
I need time to consult with our ambassador first.
Wait for my reply in Hong Kong.
Mister, they say this is a serious matter.
Rocky told me to help you...
But this Is an expensive case,
to save our organisation.
I may not see you again. Bye.
Duke Togo.
Or Golgo 131 You're under
arrest for murdering Chou.
I have other questions.
Why stay In the same hotel
as Polansky, here and in Tokyo?
It can't be a coincidence.
This Is not Hong Kong. You
have no jurisdiction here.
You are right. The Japanese
police should be here.
Wait.
Take it out.
Together with an infrared alarm system,
even an ant can't get in.
Neither can the FBI.
You've done a good job, Gaston.
Your crisis is my crisis.
You want us to investigate Polansky?
He's definitely Golgo's next target.
We can't lose him, after Chou.
Why is Polansky a target?
Golgo knows the reason, He's
surely back in Hong Kong.
Get me around 15 men.
Fifteen? An excellent detective like
you needs so many to catch a sniper?
All the cops In the Hong
Kong Police are excellent.
You don't realise who Golgo 13 is.
He's the strongest man I've ever met.
He calculates everything precisely.
Did you find him?
- No.
He can't stay in a hotel.
He must be around here.
Chen speaking. We found Golgo.
Roger. Arrest him,
- Without a warrant?
Arrest him, I said.
He seems to have a gun.
Stop him for questioning.
I'll do it.
- Go ahead!
He's heading your way.
Men, after Golgo!
Roger!
- Roger.
That's him.
This way.
What is he doing?
That's Golgol Get him!
He got off the bus and
is heading to Yumachil. After him!
Roger. That way.
Mister. She's calling you.
Why did you run away?
You killed Chou, eh? Spit it out!
How long will you keep silent?
"No comment" won't pass here.
Why, you!
We know you're the fourth sniper
hired by the US syndicate.
But why are you after Polansky?
Is it the syndicate's request?
Why are you after him? What's your intention?
It's all right to stay quiet forever.
Polansky will be safe as long as you are here.
Even you can't shoot him
from a police cell, can you?
We have plenty of time.
It's a game of endurance, between you and me.
You've held out overnight, Togo.
But there's a long way to go.
Don't forget that this is Hong Kong.
Captain!
- What is it?
Mr Wang wants you. Keep watch.
Are you releasing him?
We lost our reason for keeping him.
He didn't kill Chou.
The bullets from Chou's body and in
Li's room were from a Magnum Special.
What's Golgo's gun?
- Armalite MAS.
The dead woman was a notorious
South American killer.
Who killed her?
I don't know.
There's no evidence, even if Golgo did it.
Captain!
He's free to go.
- Really? But why?
It can't be helped.
We have information that
Polansky is on the move.
Track him down.
We're counting on you.
He's going to the US Embassy.
What? Why...
Wait.
He doesn't say anything unnecessary.
Chen, watch him.
I've been waiting for you, Golgo 13.
I knew you would be released from
the police, for lack of evidence.
It was your plan to stay in custody,
but you didn't expect me.
What can you do with no weapon?
Go to hell!
Tell them Schlitz did it, Golgo 13.
Who ordered you?
You knew it's difficult to aim at a falling object.
We lost Golgo.
This is Sminny. Join us immediately.
Roger.
He'll try to run to the US Embassy.
Don't let him.
But no violence.
USA GENERAL CONSULATE
HONG KONG
No good. Hurry!
Keep on chasing him.
Captain! Let's break in there.
Diplomatic immunity. We can't go any further.
The man from the other day is injured. There.
Come on.
Terrible wounds! You must see a doctor at once.
No doctor. Get me a knife.
Bandages.
We got some reports on Polansky.
Laos, Burma, Thailand...
Various Asian countries
have been sending him presents.
They passed Customs without inspection.
They must have been drugs.
Chou and Li-Hua were close to Polansky.
Arrest him before he escapes to the US.
But there's the diplomatic immunity.
Extra-territorial rights and diplomatic immunity.
He's dealing drugs under
those rights. Arrest him.
I'm sorry, Captain, for losing Golgo
at such a vital time.
That's all right. He hasn't done his job yet.
We'll have another chance to catch Golgo.
We'll get him.
Are you feeling any better?
You don't say a word.
You don't ask me anything, either.
Even though you know I'm...
a murderer.
They say the man I killed was my pimp.
But he was worse than a pimp, a dirty flea.
He had many other girls.
But he clung to me just for money.
I was wrong, too.
Living dirty on a boat like this,
I was prone to fall for the wrong man.
That's the fate of a woman like me.
1 fall for anyone who can say sweet words.
I was lonely. But my sister was different.
She was only 15.
That scoundrel raped her.
And she killed herself.
I couldn't forgive him.
Your first shot was from anger.
The second from fear.
The third from love.
You didn't want him to suffer.
Hold me. Hold me tight.
You're able to stand up.
Who are you?
It's okay. You don't have to tell me.
Let's celebrate your recovery.
I'll prepare a feast.
They look nice.
I'll buy some of these.
Thank you.
Captain, I found the girl.
Look at these, so many...
Who are you?
- Come on out!
What are you doing?
What are you doing? Stop it.
Where's Golgo?
- I don't know.
Where did he go? Where are you hiding him?
I don't know.
- Spit it out!
Hold it.
He won't return here. He's gone.
He's gone after his target.
Wet suits, a rope, an underwater gun...
And Armalite M16, eh?
I need more power. Get me an Anschutz 22.
Your orders are always urgent and difficult.
By tonight, okay?
Tonight?
What are you going to do?
Sorry, I shouldn't question you.
Sminny, please.
What?
Who is this speaking?
Hello? Hold the line.
Polansky has left his consul
and sought shelter at Sekirei Island.
Please make the necessary arrangements.
No more investigation.
- What?
An order from above. The
FBI will take care of him.
Polansky's asylum request
to the US was successful.
The list of the drug syndicates served him well.
The FBI will do a round-up.
That may settle the American side.
But what about us, the Hong Kong Police?
Leaving us this drug network...
The very top man is running away.
Do we just watch him go?
Without doing anything?
I'll get Polansky with my own hands.
It's a superior's order. Don't ignore it.
I'm prepared to be fired.
I won't get you in any trouble.
Boss. It's nearly time.
Yes.
A boat should be arriving soon.
The FBI's special boat.
You'll be in the States soon.
Please make arrangements for me, too.
Why, of course.
Gaston, This island Is in
your hands in the meantime.
The Hong Kong Police have retreated.
Golgo is missing.
It's safe, hiding here.
We owe everything to this file.
I get it.
Boss, the boat is coming.
So early?
Oh, the cops!
Come on.
Hong Kong Police?
- What?
It must be Sminny.
What's wrong?
Don't let them get down from here.
You guys, follow me.
Damn. The FBI boat can't reach the island.
What about the back?
It's infested, too.
What's up?
- He shot our cameras.
Isn't Golgo here?
Not yet, Captain.
Golgo will be here, for sure.
Damn you.
Wait.
Haven't you found Sminny yet?
Stop being so slow. Get Sminny.
Find him quickly.
I'll go. Get a helicopter.
Right away, Boss.
Boss, they've broken in. The cops are coming.
Damn it.
Leave it to me, Boss. I have an idea.
Where's Polansky? That's Polansky. After him!
Polansky Is trying to escape.
- What!
After that boat!
Stop the boat!
We order you to stop the boat.
Stop the boat.
Stop it!
- Stop!
The trap worked.
Damn! It's not Polansky. It's a decoy.
We were tricked?
Golgo. He must have been
waiting for that helicopter.
Hurry up! Go back.
I'm Watson, FBI.
- Polansky.
I'm Marla.
- Hurry, please.
Do you like helicopters?
Get over there! Quick!
Golgo had guessed Polansky
would take a helicopter
to break through the Hong Kong Police cordon.
He knew that the helicopter
would fly over this cliff
Judging from the weather conditions,
the direction of the wind
and the information Shigemune had given him.
It was an unerring judgment by a super sniper.
Everything went as he had guessed.
And it was all over.
Golgo 13, I couldn't pin anything on you after all.
But I'll catch you if you
come to Hong Kong again.
THE END
Subtitled by Marukomu