Today's Scroll: Hateful Teacher!
Brought to you by: Orange-Flash | Ko-Fi.com/OrangeFlash
Not
Noteb
Notebook
What is wrong, Sir Ken'ichi?
Oh, Hattori-kun.
Yesterday, I played a lot and ended up forgotten to do my homework.
"Homework"? Now can you explain, what exactly do you mean by that?
Well, that's...
You sure are lucky. You don't have to worry about any homeworks or exams.
What shall happen if you forgot to do your homework?
My teacher would scold me.
Hey fool!
By just imagining it, my head hurts and I get a headache.
You don't mind being scolded by your parents...
...but you're afraid of your teacher, which means your teacher must be very terrifying.
Ken-chan!
Look at the time, else you'll be late for school.
Oh no!
I'm off!
Do you have a ran-away-boy in your home?
Mum, did you informed them about Hattori-kun?
But because your dad said I must inform the police, just in case, so...
Why did you have to inform them?
We don't mind him staying, till we know where he come from.
No, if you inform the police, they'll just take him away!
Stop arguing with your mother. You don't have to scream.
Ninjin
He came from a famous celebrities' village or-so-I-heard...
Not a famous celebrities' village, but from a Ninja valley, he arrived.
Note: This is a pun on the word
"Nin" as in "Ninki" which means famous/celebrity.
Anyway, I have to see him.
He's right behind you, Mr. Cop.
Now at front of you.
There!
Below.
Up there!
Stop fooling around!
Look up! I mean it.
Enough! Stop fooling around!
Right above your head!
Allright, one last time.
I had enough of your mischief.
Hattori-kun, why are you holding a gun? Where did you picked it?
It seem to be a nice tool of that cop.
You can't possess it, you have to return it to the cop.
Is that so?
Mum, I'll return this gun!
Ken'ichi-kun!
Sir!
What are you doing? You'll be late for the school.
Yes sir!
Show me what you're holding!
You musn't bring any dangerous things to school.
It looks so real!
Throw this dangerous toy.
It IS a real gun!
Hey you! Where'd you picked up that gun from? Tell me the truth-
Well, this is...
Mr. Cop, you dropped it in my home.
How can you afford to lose your pistol like this? What kind of Cop are you?!
I'm sorry.
If you don't hurry, you'll be late for class.
Huh? Hattori-kun?
You can't come with me to the school.
What happened?
N-nothing!
Just talking with myself.
Hey! I said go back to our house!
What did you say?
Sir! If we don't hurry, we both will be late for class!
What's up with that shadow?
Help!
Wait, sir!
Mornin' kids!
But Sir, you're 30 mins late.
Ken'ichi-kun, how late!
Good morning, Yumeko-chan!
Why are you so late?
Well...
Now all of you, show me your homework...
I wonder what Hattori-kun is doing?
I'm here!
Hattori-kun!
Ken'ichi-kun, show me your homework.
But I forgot to do it!
Go and stand outside!
So he's being bullied by his teacher.
Guess I'll teach his teacher a lesson.
Huh? Where's our teacher?
Please help! Bring me down.
Someone!...
Hattori-kun, my teacher isn't a bad person.
I forgot my homework, so I'm the one at fault.
Oh, is that so?
So you're at fault.
Well, that may be true.
Come on.
Good bye!
I won't let you run away!
Serves him right!
You did got what you deserved.