Today's Scroll: I'm a Ninja!
Brought to you by: Orange-Flash | Ko-Fi.com/OrangeFlash
There! He did it!
How cool!
It's dangerous! Watch out!
Do not worry.
"Do not worry", you say? Ah, great!
there's no need to be so astonished over something like that!
Oh, shut up!
And who might you be?
I'm Hattori Kanzou, a ninja.
I'm Kenichi, I'm... err. mister.
But how'd you get in?
From this window right here!
Oh, from window. I see.
Then you are a theif?
Please calm down, Ken'ichi-uji.
I'm a Ninja!
A Ninja? Like those guys in a TV program?
A real Ninja?
Ken-chan! Who're you talking with?
Oh, it's Mum.
I'll introduce you to Hattori-kun!
But there isn't anyone except you in this room, Ken-chan!
But he's right her-
Huh? Where'd he gone to?
How weird.
Enough of playing and go to bed.
But he was really here!
You mean the TV program, right?
Go to bed already!
How strange!
There he is!
Mum!
Why are you shouting?
I saw him just now!
Cockroach?
Look!
Who is he?
Dunno.
Boy, if you don't return home, your parents will get worried.
You see...
I see!
Mummy, Hattori-kun says he is from in Iga province.
Inagaki?
Let him stay overnight.
It's too late to return home now. I'll prepare the bed for him.
I don't need a bed!
"I don't need a bed", he says
Why don't you sleep on the floor?
No, I'm comfortable here, just the way I am..
Honestly!
Ninja Hattori-kun...?
He's gone!
Ah, he's tired sleeping on the ceiling, so he's sleeping here.
I won't wake him up.
1.. 2.. 3.. 4...
It feels great to wake up early, once in a while. Today's gonna be a great day!
Mum, why did you mop the floor, so much that it slips?
When I woke up, the floor was sparkingly clean.
Also the breakfast is also ready.
And even our laundry are washed thoroughly.
But who possibly could have...?
Don't tell me...
Ken-chan!
Oh, a radish.
Mum, I've figured out who did everything.
Hattori-kun did it.
Hattori-kun did?
But who is this Hattori?
A Ninja from Iga village, Hattori Kanzou.
But where is he now?
Hey, Hattori-kun! Kanzou-kun!
Dear, I don't want a stranger to spend night in our home.
You should talk. You should have told me yesterday night only.
I see. I had headache.
What?
Water is dripping from ceiling.
Even though it's sunny outside.
What?
What's going on?
That boy is Hattori Kanzou?
He's cleaning the top.
Ah, watch out!
Don't move!
Stay still!
Thanks for catching me!
I guess I'll have to inform the cops.
No way! He just came here yesterday!
But Hattori-kun's parents will be worried dead!
Today's Sunday.
Don't inform the cops. It's their day off. Please?
I wonder if it'll be okay for him to stay in our home?
Are you gonna take a nap on ceiling again?
Yes, I'm not used to sleeping on the floor.
Wait up!
I can't sleep with my eyes up, if you sleep on the ceiling.
Why don't you hang a futon?
Phew! I'm relieved now.
Good night
The wet futon looks like cross-shaped shuriken.
It's embarrassing...
I never expected that a Ninja would wet his bed....