The Oblivia Region Skies
Latios, escape!
You guys must be the Pokémon Nappers!
Don't interfere!
Who on Earth are you?!
Deep red goggles and a yellow scarf...
A Pokémon Ranger, huh?
Let's go, Mukuhawk!
We'll fight those guys off!
Ranger Union
They love Pokémon and work together with their Pokémon...
...in order to protect the nature and peace.
That's what Pokémon Rangers do.
The young Ranger Natsuya has been given a new mission.
Taking action against the Pokémon Nappers, who have been poaching and selling Pokémon,
is our most important task as Pokémon Rangers.
Those Nappers have increased their activity in the Oblivia region.
And this is your task: I want you to head to the Oblivia region immediately.
Protect the Pokémon and force the Pokémon nappers to disband.
Understood.
All right. Mukuhawk, lend me your power!
Capture on!
Capture complete!
Using the Capture Styler, Pokémon Rangers are able to link their hearts With that of their Pokémon.
I'm counting on you, Mukuhawk!
And this is how Natsuya headed to the Oblivia region.
Let's go, Mukuhawk! We'll fight those guys off!
What about Latios?
Not now!
We'll withdraw for now!
I won't let you go away!
After an abrupt encounter with the Pokémon Nappers, Natsuya takes up pursuit.
But just then..
Boss Red Eye!
A Pokémon Ranger, huh?
Drop Island
Natsuya, Having crash-landed,..
has been stranded on Drop Island, a part of the Oblivia region.
Pichu?
It's all right, I'm not anyone suspicious in particular.
Pichu is alert; do not approach it carelessly.
The Capture Styler has an application called "Voice Navi".
Capture Styler
It's a support system which provides the Pokémon Ranger with various kinds of information.
Pichu, I want you to know...
..that I'm not your enemy.
Capture on!
Will Natsuya be able to capture Pichu?
The mission that Pokémon Ranger Natsuya has been given...
...has only just begun!