They link their hearts with that of their Pokémon...
...and lend the power of Pokémon in order to solve cases - that's what Pokémon Rangers do.
This time's mission is to..
...stop the Pokémon Nappers, who attempt to control Pokémon in the Oblivia region.
Pokémon Ranger Natsuya, who has been assigned the mission,
fights the Pokémon Nappers targeting Latios but crash-landed onto a beach!
Having stranded on Island, Natsuya...
...meets a Pichu extremely wary of him.
Pichu, I want you to know that I'm not an enemy of yours!
Capture on!
By capturing them, Pokémon Rangers...
...are able to link their hearts with that of the Pokemen.
It's not only effective when they need Pokémon to lend them their strength, but also when soothing them.
Capture complete!
Piehu, are you all right?
I'm Pokémon Ranger, Natsuya.
I'm not your enemy by any means.
The Pichu holding an ukulele saw the Pokémon of the island getting captured by the Pokémon Nappers...
...and apparently started seeing humans as its enemy.
Having listened to accounts from Booker, a carpenter Pichu has befriended, Natsuya...
...heads to Rainbow Island where the Nappers are said to lurk.
Rainbow Island
After arriving on Rainbow Island, Natsuya follows Pichu's lead and advances further info the forest.
Yasuri Cave
What awaits him there?
It's Pokémon Nappers.
Wait!
Hey...
You're not allowed to enter.
Hey, you're pretty good!
The light...
Wonder what the Nappers are up to?
Pichu!
Wait for me!
What's with that thing?
Don't bother with it. Once we take that thingy we have no reason to be here any more.
Zugaidos, do it!
Pichu!
You are...
...the Nappers!
Pichu!
Zugaidos, show them.
Wait!
Zugaidos is being manipulated by the enemy.
Yeah, I know.
Zugaidos, snap out of it!
Capture on!
Capture complete!
Zugaidos, you're free now!
Let's go, Pichu!
We'll now return to the headquarters.
Roger that!
Nappers!
Farewell!
This voice is...!
Boss Red Eye.
Could this be...?
Raikou!
A Raikou, huh...
The legendary Pokémon Raikou has suddenly appeared.
What is the meaning behind its appearance?
As Natsuya heads into the climax of his mission, he faces an even bigger mystery than ever before!